A Guide to the Chesapeake Western Railway Company Records, 1928-1982: SC 0154
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
- Series 2: Reports, 1953-1981
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, January 1978 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, February 1978 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, March 1978 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, April 1978 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, May 1978 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, June 1978 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, July 1978 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, August 1978 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, September 1978 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, October 1978 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, November 1978 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, December 1978 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, January 1979 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, February 1979 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, March 1979 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, April 1979 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, May 1979 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, June 1979 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, July 1979 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, August 1979 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, September 1979 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, October 1979 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, November 1979 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, December 1979 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, January 1980 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, February 1980 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, March 1980 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, April 1980 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, May 1980 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, June 1980 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, July 1980 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, August 1980 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, September 1980 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, October 1980 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, November 1980 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, December 1980 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, January 1981 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, February 1981 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, March 1981 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, April 1981 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, May 1981 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, June 1981 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, July 1981 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, August 1981 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, September 1981 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, October 1981 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, November 1981 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Time Return & Delay Reports, December 1981 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Conductor's Car Records and Tonnage Reports 14A, February-September 1980 (Box OV 4, Folder 1)
  - Conductor's Car Records and Tonnage Reports 14A, October 1980-February 1981 (Box OV 4, Folder 2)
  - Conductor's Car Records and Tonnage Reports 14A, March-July 1981 (Box OV 4, Folder 3)
  - Conductor's Car Records and Tonnage Reports 14A, August-December 1981 (Box OV 4, Folder 4)
  - Conductor's Car Records and Tonnage Reports 14A, January-June 1982 (Box OV 4, Folder 5)
  - Shipping logs, 14B: A-Mc, 1970-1977 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Shipping logs, 14B: M-Z, 1970-1977 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Traffic Analyses and other shipping records, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Traffic Analyses and other shipping records, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Traffic Analyses and other shipping records, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Traffic Analyses and other shipping records, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Traffic Analyses and other shipping records, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Traffic Analyses and other shipping records, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Traffic Analyses and other shipping records, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Traffic Analyses and other shipping records, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Traffic Analyses and other shipping records, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15C (folder 1 of 4), 1953 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15C (folder 2 of 4), 1953 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15C (folder 3 of 4), 1953 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15C (folder 4 of 4), 1953 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15D (folder 1 of 4), 1954 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15D (folder 2 of 4), 1954 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15D (folder 3 of 4), 1954 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15D (folder 4 of 4), 1954 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15E (folder 1 of 4), 1955 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15E (folder 2 of 4), 1955 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15E (folder 3 of 4), 1955 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15E (folder 4 of 4), 1955 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15F (folder 1 of 5), 1956 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15F (folder 2 of 5), 1956 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15F (folder 3 of 5), 1956 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15F (folder 4 of 5), 1956 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15F (folder 5 of 5), 1956 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15G (folder 1 of 4), 1957 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15G (folder 2 of 4), 1957 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15G (folder 3 of 4), 1957 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15G (folder 4 of 4), 1957 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15H (folder 1 of 4), 1958 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15H (folder 2 of 4), 1958 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15H (folder 3 of 4), 1958 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15H (folder 4 of 4), 1958 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15I (folder 1 of 5), 1959 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15I (folder 2 of 5), 1959 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15I (folder 3 of 5), 1959 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15I (folder 4 of 5), 1959 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15I (folder 5 of 5), 1959 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15J (folder 1 of 4), 1960 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15J (folder 2 of 4), 1960 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15J (folder 3 of 4), 1960 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15J (folder 4 of 4), 1960 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15K (folder 1 of 5), 1961 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15K (folder 2 of 5), 1961 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15K (folder 3 of 5), 1961 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15K (folder 4 of 5), 1961 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15K (folder 5 of 5), 1961 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15L (folder 1 of 4), 1962 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15L (folder 2 of 4), 1962 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15L (folder 3 of 4), 1962 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15L (folder 4 of 4), 1962 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15M (folder 1 of 4), 1963 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15M (folder 2 of 4), 1963 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15M (folder 3 of 4), 1963 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15M (folder 4 of 4), 1963 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15N (folder 1 of 3), 1964 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15N (folder 2 of 3), 1964 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15N (folder 3 of 3), 1964 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15O (folder 1 of 3), 1966 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15O (folder 2 of 3), 1966 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15O (folder 3 of 3), 1966 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15P (folder 1 of 3), 1967 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15P (folder 2 of 3), 1967 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15P (folder 3 of 3), 1967 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15Q (folder 1 of 4), 1968 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15Q (folder 2 of 4), 1968 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15Q (folder 3 of 4), 1968 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15Q (folder 4 of 4), 1968 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15R (folder 1 of 2), 1969 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15R (folder 2 of 2), 1969 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15S (folder 1 of 3), 1970 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15S (folder 2 of 3), 1970 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Per Diem/Mileage and Transfer Books, 15S (folder 3 of 3), 1970 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Series 3: Account Books, 1932-1974
  Series 3: Account Books, 1932-1974, contains: Interline Freight Balances; Car Services Balances; Amounts Due From and To Foreign Companies on Interline Freight Accounts; Operating Expenses and REvenues and other information including shops, engine house, bridges, agents, conductors, donations, etc.; Per Diem Reclaim Records, 1952-1973; Income Statements, 1968-1971; Records of Vouchers Released, 1955-1967; Freight Car Hires, 1943-1975, summarizing car hire, passenger and freight car mileage; and Miscellaneous accounts, 1934-1951, containing detailed information of topics organized chronologically and categorically under the following headings: Operating Revenues, Freight Revenues, Rent from Locomotives, Miscellaneous Income, Maintenance, Transportation Improvements, and Statements for Depreciation for railway structures. Balance in Interline Freight Accounts, 1932-1935, lists date, items, folio number, and debits with yearly balances, organized alphabetically by account name. Car Services Balance Books, 1944-1971, record balance and payment information for interline car service accounts. Record of Amounts Due From and To Foreign Companies on Interline Freight Accounts Journals, 1930-1944, comprise both operating expenses and revenues as well as other information.
  - Balance in Interline Freight Accounts, unbound Volume 9A, ACL Ry Co - CS+StL Ry, 1932-1938 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Balance in Interline Freight Accounts, unbound Volume 9A, D+HRR Co - M+G Ry Co, 1932-1938 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Balance in Interline Freight Accounts, unbound Volume 9A, Yahdin - Norfolk+Western, 1932-1938 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Balance in Interline Freight Accounts, unbound Volume 9A, Federal Rds - CRI+P Ry, 1932-1938 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Balance in Interline Freight Accounts, unbound Volume 9A, Chic Rk Isl+Pac - Ill No, 1932-1938 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Balance in Interline Freight Accounts, unbound Volume 9A, Imp Extr - NY Phila+Norfolk, 1932-1938 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Balance in Interline Freight Accounts, unbound Volume 9A, Oregon Short - Wisc Central, 1932-1938 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Car Services Balance Book, 9B, January 1944-March 1952 (Box OV 1)
  - Car Services Balance Book, 9C, A-B with Accounts 7113, 752, 759 preceding, 1953-1971 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Car Services Balance Book, 9C, C-G, 1953-1972 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Car Services Balance Book, 9C, H-P, 1953-1971 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Car Services Balance Book, 9C, Q-Z, 1953-1972 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Records of Amounts Due From and To Foreign Companies on Interline Freight Accounts, 9D, January 1955-September 1956 (Box OV 2, Folder 1)
  - Records of Amounts Due From and To Foreign Companies on Interline Freight Accounts, 9D, October 1956-November 1958 (Box OV 2, Folder 2)
  - Records of Amounts Due From and To Foreign Companies on Interline Freight Accounts, 9D, December 1958-October 1960 (Box OV 2, Folder 3)
  - Records of Amounts Due From and To Foreign Companies on Interline Freight Accounts, 9D, November 1960-September 1962 (Box OV 3, Folder 1)
  - Records of Amounts Due From and To Foreign Companies on Interline Freight Accounts, 9D, October 1962-September 1964 (Box OV 3, Folder 2)
  - Records of Amounts Due From and To Foreign Companies on Interline Freight Accounts, 9D, October 1964-December 1967 (Box OV 3, Folder 3)
  - Records of Amounts Due From and To Foreign Companies on Interline Freight Accounts, 9E, January 1968-December 1970 (Box OV 4, Folder 1)
  - Records of Amounts Due From and To Foreign Companies on Interline Freight Accounts, 9E, January 1971-February 1974 (Box OV 4, Folder 2)
  - Journal 9F [stamped No. 8], pp. 1-140, January 1930-September 1933 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Journal 9F [stamped No. 8], pp. 141-260, January 1930-September 1933 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Journal 9F [stamped No. 8], pp. 261-380, January 1930-September 1933 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Journal 9F [stamped No. 8], pp. 381-500, January 1930-September 1933 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Journal 9G [stamped No. 9], pp. 1-120, October 1933-June 1936 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Journal 9G [stamped No. 9], pp. 121-240, October 1933-June 1936 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Journal 9G [stamped No. 9], pp. 241-360, October 1933-June 1936 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Journal 9G [stamped No. 9], pp. 361-480, October 1933-June 1936 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Journal 9G [stamped No. 9], pp. 481-600, October 1933-June 1936 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Journal 9H [stamped No. 10], pp. 1-116, July 1936 - June 1939 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Journal 9H [stamped No. 10], pp. 117-236, July 1936 - June 1939 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Journal 9H [stamped No. 10], pp. 237-356, July 1936 - June 1939 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Journal 9H [stamped No. 10], pp. 357-500, July 1936 - June 1939 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Journal 9I [stamped No. 11], pp. 1-140, July 1936-May 1944 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Journal 9I [stamped No. 11], pp. 141-256, July 1936-May 1944 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Journal 9I [stamped No. 11], pp. 257-376, July 1936-May 1944 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Journal 9I [stamped No. 11], pp. 377-500, July 1936-May 1944 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Per Diem Reclaim Records, January-September 1952 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Per Diem Reclaim Records, October 1952-August 1953 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Per Diem Reclaim Records, September 1953-June 1954 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Per Diem Reclaim Records, July 1954-March 1955 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Per Diem Reclaim Records, April-December 1955 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Per Diem Reclaim Records, January-August 1956 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Per Diem Reclaim Records, September 1956-May 1957 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Per Diem Reclaim Records, June-December 1957 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Per Diem Reclaim Records, January-July 1958 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Per Diem Reclaim Records, August 1958-March 1959 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Per Diem Reclaim Records, April-December 1959 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Per Diem Reclaim Records, January-June 1960 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Per Diem Reclaim Records, July-December 1960 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Per Diem Reclaim Records, January-June 1961 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Per Diem Reclaim Records, July-December 1961 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Per Diem Reclaim Records, January-August 1962 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Per Diem Reclaim Records, September 1962-April 1963 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Per Diem Reclaim Records, May-August 1963 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Per Diem Reclaim Records, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Per Diem Reclaim Records, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Per Diem Reclaim Records, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Per Diem Reclaim Records, January-July 1967 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Per Diem Reclaim Records, January-July 1967 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Per Diem Reclaim Records, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Per Diem Reclaim Records, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Per Diem Reclaim Records, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Per Diem Reclaim Records, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Per Diem Reclaim Records, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Per Diem Reclaim Records, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Income Statement, January 1968-November 1971 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Records of Vouchers Released, May 1955-December 1967 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Freight Car Hire, 11A, 1943-1975 (Box OV 1, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Accounts, 11B (folder 1 of 9), 1934-1951 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Accounts, 11B (folder 2 of 9), 1934-1951 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Accounts, 11B (folder 3 of 9), 1934-1951 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Accounts, 11B (folder 4 of 9), 1934-1951 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Accounts, 11B (folder 5 of 9), 1934-1951 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Accounts, 11B (folder 6 of 9), 1934-1951 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Accounts, 11B (folder 7 of 9), 1934-1951 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Accounts, 11B (folder 8 of 9), 1934-1951 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Accounts, 11B (folder 9 of 9), 1934-1951 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Series 4: Correspondence, 1976-1979
  Series 4: Correspondence, 1976-1979, is comprised of a variety of topics which include land leases, shipments, track upgrades, expense reports, and business agreements in chronological order.
  - Correspondence, January 1976 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, February 1976 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, March 1976 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, April 1976 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, May 1976 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, June 1976 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, July 1976 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, August 1976 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, September 1976 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, October 1976 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, November 1976 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, December 1976 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, January-February 1977 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, March-April 1977 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, May-June 1977 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence, July-August 1977 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, September-October 1977 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, November-December 1977 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, January 1979 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence, February 1979 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, March 1979 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, April 1979 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence, May 1979 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, June 1979 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence, July 1979 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, August 1979 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence, September 1979 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence, October 1979 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, November 1979 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence, December 1979 (Box 21, Folder 42)
- Series 5: Miscellaneous Documents, 1928-1982
  Series 5: Miscellaneous Documents, 1928-1982, is comprised of eclectic pieces--many relating to previous series that would be lost among more substantial predecessors. Headings under Miscellaneous include: Financial notes and documents, many handwritten, 1935-1938 and undated; a conductor's balance sheet from September 1935; Operating expenses, undated; Per Diem Reclaim Mileage Records and Record of Amounts Due From and To Foreign Companies on Interline Freight Accounts, September 1935; Reports of Interline Passenger Traffic, August 1935 [one of which contains a note in the "Remarks" column stating "CCC" perhaps indicating a one way trip to Bridgewater Station for members of the Civilian Conservation Corps.]; Documents and invoices for parts and repair, indemnity releases, etc., 1955-1976; Forms from printing companies, 1928-1968; Records of purchase for forms from local printers; Receipt books, Carload Traffic Received, Automobile Expenses Records, Forecast Statement, N&W strike letter, 3.5 acre lease letter to Virginia Electric and Power Company, 1975-1980; Staunton Textile Corporation and Celanese Corporation, 1934-1955; Miscellaneous Correspondence, freight bills, account information, etc. and Exxon records, 1974-1976.
  - Financial notes and documents, 1928-1980 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Invoices, 1928-1980 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Forms from printing companies, 1928-1980 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Miscellany, 1928-1980 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Receipt books, 1928-1980 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Staunton Textile Corp. and Celanese Corp. Documents, 1928-1980 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Exxon Records, 1928-1980 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Series 6: Publications, 1963-1977
  Series 6: Publications, 1963-1977, include copies of Bullinger's Postal and Shipper's Guide for the US and Canada, 1963, which lists shipping rates, distances, etc. and Standard Transportation Commodity Code Tariff No. 1-E, November 15, 1977.
  - Bullinger's Postal and Shipper's Guide for the US and Canada, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Standard Transportation Commodity Code Tariff No. 1-E, November 15, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 44)
- Series 7: Blueprints and Schematics, 1951-1979
  Series 7: Blueprints and Schematics, 1951-1979, contains the oversize materials: a blueprint of the railway line from 1951 and diagrams of electircal gates and signal wiring, 1961-1979.
  - Blueprint of railroad between two stations, 15A, 1951 (Storage 1)
  - Diagrams of electrical gates of signal wiring, 15B, 1961-1979 (Storage 1)